hdwallpapersuk.com 2013-12-15

# Privacy Policy | HD Wallpapers UK

#### What is privacy policy?

The privacy of our users keep, its prime importance for us and we take the privacy of our users very seriously. This document of privacy informs that how we deal with the personal identifiable data of our users. This document also informs that how we deal with third party advertisers. 

#### Personal data: 

We highly discourage, if any of our visitor want to leave any kind of its personal data to our website. Your personal information will be of no use for us and through our website it can come under the vision of some wrong approach. So we highly recommend, if any visitor of our website will not leave its personal data on our website. We also highly discourage the visiting of our website from a person, who is of un-adequate age. The under-aged persons should have to visit our website, after the permission of its guardian. 

#### Server Logs Data:

We also collect data about web, database, our site access information, and server software usage. There would be different kind of information like IP address, the area from where you are accessing our website or your geographical location. All the information that we collect from the servers of our visitors, will be used for improving the experience of use of our website for our visitors. 

#### Third party advertisements:

Our servers get the advertisements from Google Adsense, Infolinks, and quite a number of other third party advertisers. This is not included in our privacy policy to give information about the privacy policy of our advertisers. For their privacy policies, our visitors should have to visit their sites first for getting a comprehensive idea about their privacy policies.

#### Data sharing or selling:

We strongly condemn the practice of selling data to anyone for any purpose. Therefore, once you are interacting with our website, you must never be worried about us selling your data to marketers. We respect your privacy the way we respect our own privacy. 

#### Data Maintenance:

We only retain, create backups of data, and copy it to other machines or servers for dealing with server crises and problems. There is no hidden purpose or ill intention behind retaining your data except for backup.
